<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Combined Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://github.com/Bizza12345/CTI-RSS</link>
    <description>A combined feed of various cybersecurity RSS feeds</description>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4415 - Apple Releases Security Updates Addressing Actively Exploited Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4415</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Two exploited zero-day vulnerabilities in Safari, iOS, iPadOS and macOS Sonoma could lead to arbitrary code execution or&amp;nbsp;unauthorised access&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Two exploited zero-day vulnerabilities in Safari, iOS, iPadOS and macOS Sonoma could lead to arbitrary code execution or unauthorised access&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 05 Dec 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4416 - Zyxel Releases Security Update</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4416</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Update addresses three critical and three high&amp;nbsp;vulnerabilities in several Network Attached Storage (NAS) devices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Update addresses three critical and three high vulnerabilities in several Network Attached Storage (NAS) devices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 05 Dec 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4413 - Foxit Releases Security Updates</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4413</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Security updates address multiple vulnerabilities affecting Foxit Reader and Foxit PDF Editor that could allow attackers to perform remote code execution on vulnerable systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Security updates address multiple vulnerabilities affecting Foxit Reader and Foxit PDF Editor that could allow attackers to perform remote code execution on vulnerable systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 01 Dec 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4414 - Google Releases Security Update Addressing Multiple Vulnerabilities in Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4414</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Security update addresses six high severity vulnerabilities in Google Chrome, including an actively exploited zero-day vulnerability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Security update addresses six high severity vulnerabilities in Google Chrome, including an actively exploited zero-day vulnerability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 29 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4412 - ownCloud releases Security Advisories</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4412</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The security advisories address three critical vulnerabilities with one being reported as exploited in the wild&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The security advisories address three critical vulnerabilities with one being reported as exploited in the wild&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 28 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-1899 - WordPress CAPTCHA Plugin Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2018/cc-1899</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A backdoor has been discovered in the WordPress plugin &quot;Captcha free plugin&quot;, by BestWebSoft. BestWebSoft has recently sold the plugin to an undisclosed buyer, who then updated the plugin with a backdoor. This backdoor granted the plugin's new author administrative privileges to the website without any authentication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; A backdoor has been discovered in the WordPress plugin &quot;Captcha free plugin&quot;, by BestWebSoft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 23 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4411 - Critical Vulnerability in CrushFTP</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4411</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The critical vulnerability assigned CVE-2023-43177 could allow remote code execution on affected devices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The critical vulnerability assigned CVE-2023-43177 could allow remote code execution on affected devices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 20 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4370 - Exploitation of CVE-2023-38831 in WinRAR</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4370</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;RARLabs WinRAR file extension spoofing exploit seen in the wild&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; RARLabs WinRAR file extension spoofing exploit seen in the wild&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 20 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4407 - Fortinet Releases Multiple Security Advisories</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4407</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The security advisories address two critical, two high, one medium and two low vulnerabilities impacting FortiClient, FortiGate and FortiSIEM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The security advisories address two critical, two high, one medium and two low vulnerabilities impacting FortiClient, FortiGate and FortiSIEM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 16 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CC-4409 - VMware Releases Critical Security Update for VMware Cloud Director Appliance</title>
      <link>https://digital.nhs.uk/cyber-alerts/2023/cc-4409</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Severity: Medium&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Security update addresses an authentication bypass vulnerability in the&amp;nbsp;VMware Cloud Director Appliance platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Security update addresses an authentication bypass vulnerability in the VMware Cloud Director Appliance platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Updated: 15 Nov 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/05/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CISA released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on December 5, 2023. These advisories provide timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;ICSA-23-339-01 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-23-339-01&quot;&gt;Zebra ZTC Industrial ZT400 and Desktop GK420d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ICSA-23-208-03 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-23-208-03&quot;&gt;Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series (Update D)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;CISA encourages users and administrators to review the newly released ICS advisories for technical details and mitigations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/05/cisa-adds-four-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CISA has added four new vulnerabilities to its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&quot;&gt;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&lt;/a&gt;, based on evidence of active exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-33106&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-33106&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-33106&lt;/a&gt; Qualcomm Multiple Chipsets Use of Out-of-Range Pointer Offset Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-33063&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-33063&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-33063&lt;/a&gt; Qualcomm Multiple Chipsets Use-After-Free Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-33107&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-33107&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-33107&lt;/a&gt; Qualcomm Multiple Chipsets Integer Overflow Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2022-22071&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2022-22071&quot;&gt;CVE-2022-22071&lt;/a&gt; Qualcomm Multiple Chipsets Use-After-Free Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/binding-operational-directive-22-01&quot; title=&quot;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the&lt;a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/Reducing_the_Significant_Risk_of_Known_Exploited_Vulnerabilities_211103.pdf&quot; title=&quot;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&quot;&gt;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Catalog vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Catalog vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities&quot; title=&quot;specified criteria&quot;&gt;specified criteria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Adobe ColdFusion CVE-2023-26360 for Initial Access to Government Servers</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-339a</link>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) is releasing a Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) in response to confirmed exploitation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-26360&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-26360&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-26360&lt;/a&gt; by unidentified threat actors at a Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agency. This vulnerability presents as an improper access control issue impacting Adobe ColdFusion versions 2018 Update 15 (and earlier) and 2021 Update 5 (and earlier). CVE-2023-26360 also affects ColdFusion 2016 and ColdFusion 11 installations; however, they are no longer supported since they reached end of life. Exploitation of this CVE can result in arbitrary code execution. Following the FCEB agency’s investigation, analysis of network logs confirmed the compromise of at least two public-facing servers within the environment between June and July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This CSA provides network defenders with tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), indicators of compromise (IOCs), and methods to detect and protect against similar exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Download the PDF version of this report:&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/aa23-339a-threat-actors-exploit-adobe-coldfusion-cve-2023-26360.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-339A Threat Actors Exploit Adobe ColdFusion CVE-2023-26360 for Initial Access to Government Servers&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(PDF,       449.49 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a downloadable copy of IOCs, see:&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/AA23-339A.stix_.xml&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-339A STIX XML&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(XML,       23.83 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/AA23-339A-Threat-Actors-Exploit-Adobe-ColdFusion-CVE-2023-26360-for-Initial-Access-to-Government-Servers.stix_.json&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-339A STIX JSON&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(JSON,       23.29 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TECHNICAL DETAILS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This advisory uses the &lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/&quot;&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt; for Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; framework, version 14. See the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Tactics and Techniques section for tables mapped to the threat actors’ activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adobe ColdFusion is a commercial application server used for rapid web-application development. ColdFusion supports proprietary markup languages for building web applications and integrates external components like databases and other third-party libraries. ColdFusion uses a proprietary language, ColdFusion Markup Language (CFML), for development but the application itself is built using JAVA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In June 2023, through the exploitation of CVE-2023-26360, threat actors were able to establish an initial foothold on two agency systems in two separate instances. In both incidents, Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE) alerted of the potential exploitation of an Adobe ColdFusion vulnerability on public-facing web servers in the agency’s pre-production environment. Both servers were running outdated versions of software which are vulnerable to various CVEs. Additionally, various commands were initiated by the threat actors on the compromised web servers; the exploited vulnerability allowed the threat actors to drop malware using HTTP POST commands to the directory path associated with ColdFusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analysis suggests that the malicious activity conducted by the threat actors was a reconnaissance effort to map the broader network. No evidence is available to confirm successful data exfiltration or lateral movement during either incident. &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; It is unknown if the same or different threat actors were behind each incident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As early as June 26, 2023, threat actors obtained an initial foothold on a public-facing [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1190/&quot; title=&quot;Exploit Public-Facing Application&quot;&gt;T1190&lt;/a&gt;] web server running Adobe ColdFusion v2016.0.0.3 through exploitation of CVE-2023-26360. Threat actors successfully connected from malicious IP address &lt;code&gt;158.101.73[.]241&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;/strong&gt;CISA recommends organizations investigate or vet this IP address prior to taking action, such as blocking. This IP resolves to a public cloud service provider and possibly hosts a large volume of legitimate traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The agency’s correlation of Internet Information Services (IIS) logs against open source[&lt;a href=&quot;https://packetstormsecurity.com/files/172079/Adobe-ColdFusion-Unauthenticated-Remote-Code-Execution.html&quot; title=&quot;Adobe ColdFusion Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;] information indicates that the identified uniform resource identifier (URI) &lt;code&gt;/cf_scripts/scripts/ajax/ckeditor/plugins/filemanager/iedit.cfc&lt;/code&gt; was used to exploit CVE-2023-26360. The agency removed the asset from the network within 24 hours of the MDE alert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors started process enumeration to obtain currently running processes on the web server and performed a network connectivity check, likely to confirm their connection was successful. Following additional enumeration efforts to obtain information about the web server and its operating system [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1082/&quot; title=&quot;System Information Discovery&quot;&gt;T1082&lt;/a&gt;], the threat actors checked for the presence of ColdFusion version 2018 [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1518/&quot; title=&quot;Software Discovery&quot;&gt;T1518&lt;/a&gt;]—previous checks were also conducted against version 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors were observed traversing the filesystem [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1083/&quot; title=&quot;File and Directory Discovery&quot;&gt;T1083&lt;/a&gt;] and uploading various artifacts to the web server [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1105/&quot; title=&quot;Ingress Tool Transfer&quot;&gt;T1105&lt;/a&gt;], to include deleting the file &lt;code&gt;tat.cfm&lt;/code&gt; [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1070/004/&quot; title=&quot;Indicator Removal: File Deletion&quot;&gt;T1070.004&lt;/a&gt;]. &lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;This file was deleted prior to the victim locating it on the host for analysis. Its characteristics and functionality are unknown. In addition:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Certutil[&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v13/software/S0160/&quot; title=&quot;certutil&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;] was run against &lt;code&gt;conf.txt&lt;/code&gt; [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1140/&quot; title=&quot;Deobfuscate/Decode Files or Information&quot;&gt;T1140&lt;/a&gt;] and decoded as a web shell (&lt;code&gt;config.jsp&lt;/code&gt;) [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1505/003/&quot; title=&quot;Server Software Component: Web Shell&quot;&gt;T1505.003&lt;/a&gt;],[&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1036/008/&quot; title=&quot;Masquerading: Masquerade File Type&quot;&gt;T1036.008&lt;/a&gt;]. &lt;code&gt;Conf.txt&lt;/code&gt; was subsequently deleted, likely to evade detection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;Threat actors were only observed interacting with the &lt;code&gt;config.jsp&lt;/code&gt; web shell from this point on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HTTP POST requests [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1071/001/&quot; title=&quot;Application Layer Protocol: Web Protocols&quot;&gt;T1071.001&lt;/a&gt;] were made to &lt;code&gt;config.cfm&lt;/code&gt;, an expected configuration file in a standard installation of ColdFusion [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1036/005/&quot; title=&quot;Masquerading: Match Legitimate Name or Location&quot;&gt;T1036.005&lt;/a&gt;]. Code review of &lt;code&gt;config.cfm&lt;/code&gt; indicated malicious code—intended to execute on versions of ColdFusion 9 or less—was inserted with the intent to extract username, password, and data source uniform resource locators (URLs). According to analysis, this code insertion could be used in future malicious activity by the threat actors (e.g., by using the valid credentials that were compromised). This file also contained code used to upload additional files by the threat actors; however, the agency was unable to identify the source of their origin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Threat actors attempted to run &lt;code&gt;attrib.exe&lt;/code&gt; to hide the newly created &lt;code&gt;config.jsp&lt;/code&gt; web shell [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1564/001/&quot; title=&quot;Hide Artifacts: Hidden Files and Directories&quot;&gt;T1564.001&lt;/a&gt;]. Analysis of this phase found no indication of successful execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A small subset of events generated from various ColdFusion application logs identified that &lt;code&gt;tat.cfm&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;config.jsp&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;system.cfm&lt;/code&gt; failed to execute on the host due to syntax errors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Threat actors created various files (see Table 1 below) in the C:\IBM directory using the initialization process coldfusion.exe. None of these files were located on the server (possibly due to threat actor deletion) but are assessed as likely threat actor tools. Analysts assessed the C:\IBM directory as a staging folder to support threat actors’ malicious operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; Organizations are encouraged to investigate the use of these files for related signs of compromise prior to performing remediation actions. Two artifacts are legitimate Microsoft files; threat actors were observed using these files following initial compromise for intended malicious purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 1: Threat Actor Tools&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File Name&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hash (SHA-1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;eee.exe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b6818d2d5cbd902ce23461f24fc47e24937250e6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VirusTotal[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/a3acb9f79647f813671c1a21097a51836b0b95397ebc9cd178bc806e1773c864/detection&quot; title=&quot;Virus Total GUI File&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;] flags this file as malicious. This was located in D:\$RECYCLE.BIN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;edge.exe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;75a8ceded496269e9877c2d55f6ce13551d93ff4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dynamic-link library (DLL) file &lt;code&gt;msedge.dll&lt;/code&gt; attempted to execute via &lt;code&gt;edge.exe&lt;/code&gt; but received an error.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;This file is part of the official Microsoft Edge browser and is a cookie exporter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;fscan.exe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;be332b6e2e2ed9e1e57d8aafa0c00aa77d4b8656&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analysis confirmed at least three subnets were scanned using &lt;code&gt;fscan.exe&lt;/code&gt;, which was launched from the C:\IBM directory [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1046/&quot; title=&quot;Network Service Discovery&quot;&gt;T1046&lt;/a&gt;].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RC.exe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9126b8320d18a52b1315d5ada08e1c380d18806b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;RCDLL.dll&lt;/code&gt; attempted to execute via &lt;code&gt;RC.exe&lt;/code&gt; but received an error.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This file is part of the official Windows operating system and is called Microsoft Resource Compiler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; The malicious code found on the system during this incident contained code that, when executed, would attempt to decrypt passwords for ColdFusion data sources. The seed value included in the code is a known value for ColdFusion version 8 or older—where the seed value was hard-coded. A threat actor who has control over the database server can use the values to decrypt the data source passwords in ColdFusion version 8 or older. The victim’s servers were running a newer version at the time of compromise; thus, the malicious code failed to decrypt passwords using the default hard-coded seed value for the older versions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As early as June 2, 2023, threat actors obtained an initial foothold on an additional public-facing web server running Adobe ColdFusion v2021.0.0.2 via malicious IP address &lt;code&gt;125.227.50[.]97&lt;/code&gt; through exploitation of CVE-2023-26360. Threat actors further enumerated domain trusts to identify lateral movement opportunities [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1482/&quot; title=&quot;Domain Trust Discovery&quot;&gt;T1482&lt;/a&gt;] by using &lt;code&gt;nltest&lt;/code&gt; commands. The threat actors also collected information about local [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1087/001/&quot; title=&quot;Account Discovery: Local Account&quot;&gt;T1087.001&lt;/a&gt;] and domain [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1087/002/&quot; title=&quot;Account Discovery: Domain Account&quot;&gt;T1087.002&lt;/a&gt;] administrative user accounts while performing reconnaissance by using commands such as &lt;code&gt;localgroup&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;net user&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;net user /domain&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;ID&lt;/code&gt;. Host and network reconnaissance efforts were further conducted to discover network configuration, time logs, and query user information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors were observed dropping the file &lt;code&gt;d.txt&lt;/code&gt;—decoded as &lt;code&gt;d.jsp&lt;/code&gt;—via POST command in addition to eight malicious artifacts (&lt;code&gt;hiddenfield.jsp&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;hiddenfield_jsp.class&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;hiddenfield_jsp.java&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Connection.jsp&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Connection_jsp.class&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Connection_jsp.java&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;d_jsp.class&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;d_jsp.java/&lt;/code&gt;). According to open source information, &lt;code&gt;d.jsp&lt;/code&gt; is a remote access trojan (RAT) that utilizes a JavaScript loader [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1059/007/&quot; title=&quot;Command and Scripting Interpreter: JavaScript&quot;&gt;T1059.007&lt;/a&gt;] to infect the device and requires communication with the actor-controlled server to perform actions.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stealthy-new-javascript-malware-infects-windows-pcs-with-rats/&quot; title=&quot;Stealthy new JavaScript malware infects Windows PCs with RATs&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;] The agency’s analysis identified the trojan as a modified version of a publicly available web shell code.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Tas9er/ByPassGodzilla&quot; title=&quot;Tas9er / ByPassGodzilla&quot;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;] After maintaining persistence, threat actors periodically tested network connectivity by pinging Google’s domain name system (DNS) [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1016/001/&quot;&gt;T1016.001&lt;/a&gt;]. The threat actors conducted additional reconnaissance efforts via searching for the &lt;code&gt;.jsp&lt;/code&gt; files that were uploaded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors attempted to exfiltrate the (Registry) files &lt;code&gt;sam.zip&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;sec.zip&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;blank.jsp&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;cf-bootstrap.jar&lt;/code&gt;. Windows event logs identified the actors were not successful due to the malicious activity being detected and quarantined. An additional file (&lt;code&gt;sys.zip&lt;/code&gt;) was created on the system; however, there were no indications of any attempt to exfiltrate it. Analysis identified these files resulted from executed save and compress data processes from the HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE (HKLM) Registry key, as well as save security account manager (SAM) [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1003/002/&quot; title=&quot;OS Credential Dumping: Security Account Manager&quot;&gt;T1003.002&lt;/a&gt;] information to .zip files. The SAM Registry file may allow for malicious actors to obtain usernames and reverse engineer passwords; however, no artifacts were available to confirm that the threat actors were successful in exfiltrating the SAM Registry hive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Windows event logs show that a malicious file (&lt;code&gt;1.dat&lt;/code&gt;) was detected and quarantined. Analysis determined this file was a local security authority subsystem service (LSASS) dump [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1003/001/&quot; title=&quot;OS Credential Dumping: LSASS Memory&quot;&gt;T1003.001&lt;/a&gt;] file that contained user accounts—to include multiple disabled credentials—and Windows new technology LAN manager (NTLM) passwords. The accounts were found on multiple servers across the victim’s network and were not successfully used for lateral movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As efforts for reconnaissance continued, the threat actors changed their approach to using security tools that were present on the victim server. &lt;code&gt;Esentutl.exe&lt;/code&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v13/software/S0404/&quot; title=&quot;esentutl&quot;&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;] was used to attempt this registry dump. Attempts to download data from the threat actors’ command and control (C2) server were also observed but blocked and logged by the victim server. Threat actors further attempted to access SYSVOL, which is used to deliver policy and logon scripts to domain members on an agency domain controller [&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1484/001/&quot; title=&quot;Domain Policy Modification: Group Policy Modification&quot;&gt;T1484.001&lt;/a&gt;]. The attempt was unsuccessful. Had the attempt succeeded, the threat actors may have been able to change policies across compromised servers.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://social.technet.microsoft.com/wiki/contents/articles/8548.active-directory-sysvol-and-netlogon.aspx&quot; title=&quot;Active Directory: SYSVOL and NETLOGON&quot;&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;During this incident, analysis strongly suggests that the threat actors likely viewed the data contained in the ColdFusion seed.properties file via the web shell interface. The seed.properties file contains the seed value and encryption method used to encrypt passwords. The seed values can also be used to decrypt passwords. No malicious code was found on the victim system to indicate the threat actors attempted to decode any passwords using the values found in seed.properties file. Versions of ColdFusion 9 or greater use the seed.properties file, which contains unique seed values that can only be used on a single server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK TACTICS AND TECHNIQUES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See Tables 2-9 for all referenced threat actor tactics and techniques for enterprise environments in this advisory. For assistance with mapping malicious cyber activity to the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK framework, see CISA and MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/news/best-practices-mitre-attckr-mapping&quot; title=&quot;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&quot;&gt;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&lt;/a&gt; and CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cisagov/Decider/&quot; title=&quot;cisagov / decider&quot;&gt;Decider Tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 2: Initial Access&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploit Public-Facing Application&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1190/&quot; title=&quot;Exploit Public-Facing Application&quot;&gt;T1190&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors exploited two public-facing web servers running outdated versions of Adobe ColdFusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 3: Execution&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Command and Scripting Interpreter: JavaScript&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1059/007/&quot; title=&quot;Command and Scripting Interpreter: JavaScript&quot;&gt;T1059.007&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In correlation with open source information, analysis determined &lt;code&gt;d.jsp&lt;/code&gt; is a RAT that utilizes a JavaScript loader to infect the device and requires communication with the actor-controlled server to perform actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 4: Persistence&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Server Software Component: Web Shell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1505/003/&quot; title=&quot;Server Software Component: Web Shell&quot;&gt;T1505.003&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors uploaded various web shells to enable remote code execution and to execute commands on compromised web servers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 5: Privilege Escalation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Domain Policy Modification: Group Policy Modification&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1484/001/&quot; title=&quot;Domain Policy Modification: Group Policy Modification&quot;&gt;T1484.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors attempted to edit SYSVOL on an agency domain controller to change policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 6: Defense Evasion&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Masquerading: Match Legitimate Name or Location&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1036/005/&quot; title=&quot;Masquerading: Match Legitimate Name or Location&quot;&gt;T1036.005&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors inserted malicious code with the intent to extract username, password, and data source URLs into &lt;code&gt;config.cfm&lt;/code&gt;—an expected configuration file in a standard installation of ColdFusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Masquerading: Masquerade File Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1036/008/&quot; title=&quot;Masquerading: Masquerade File Type&quot;&gt;T1036.008&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors used the .txt file extension to disguise malware files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indicator Removal: File Deletion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1070/004/&quot; title=&quot;Indicator Removal: File Deletion&quot;&gt;T1070.004&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors deleted files following upload to remove malicious indicators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deobfuscate/Decode Files or Information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1140/&quot; title=&quot;Deobfuscate/Decode Files or Information&quot;&gt;T1140&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors used &lt;code&gt;certutil&lt;/code&gt; to decode web shells hidden inside .txt files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hide Artifacts: Hidden Files and Directories&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1564/001/&quot; title=&quot;Hide Artifacts: Hidden Files and Directories&quot;&gt;T1564.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors attempted to run &lt;code&gt;attrib.exe&lt;/code&gt; to hide the newly created &lt;code&gt;config.jsp&lt;/code&gt; web shell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 7: Credential Access&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OS Credential Dumping: LSASS Memory&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1003/001/&quot; title=&quot;OS Credential Dumping: LSASS Memory&quot;&gt;T1003.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors attempted to harvest user account credentials through LSASS memory dumping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OS Credential Dumping: Security Account Manager&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1003/002/&quot; title=&quot;OS Credential Dumping: Security Account Manager&quot;&gt;T1003.002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors saved and compressed SAM information to .zip files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 8: Discovery&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System Network Configuration Discovery: Internet Connection Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1016/001/&quot; title=&quot;System Network Configuration Discovery: Internet Connection Discovery&quot;&gt;T1016.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors periodically tested network connectivity by pinging Google’s DNS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network Service Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1046/&quot; title=&quot;Network Service Discovery&quot;&gt;T1046&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors scanned at least three subnets to gather network information using &lt;code&gt;fscan.exe&lt;/code&gt;, to include administrative data for future exfiltration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System Information Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1082/&quot; title=&quot;System Information Discovery&quot;&gt;T1082&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors collected information about the web server and its operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;File and Directory Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1083/&quot; title=&quot;File and Directory Discovery&quot;&gt;T1083&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors traversed and were able to search through folders on the victim’s web server filesystem. Additional reconnaissance efforts were conducted via searching for the &lt;code&gt;.jsp&lt;/code&gt; files that were uploaded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Account Discovery: Local Account&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1087/001/&quot; title=&quot;Account Discovery: Local Account&quot;&gt;T1087.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors collected information about local user accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Account Discovery: Domain Account&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1087/002/&quot; title=&quot;Account Discovery: Domain Account&quot;&gt;T1087.002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors collected information about domain users, including identification of domain admin accounts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Domain Trust Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1482/&quot; title=&quot;Domain Trust Discovery&quot;&gt;T1482&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors enumerated domain trusts to identify lateral movement opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1518/&quot; title=&quot;Software Discovery&quot;&gt;T1518&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following initial access and enumeration, threat actors checked for the presence of ColdFusion version 2018 on the victim web server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 9: Command and Control&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Application Layer Protocol: Web Protocols&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1071/001/&quot; title=&quot;Application Layer Protocol: Web Protocols&quot;&gt;T1071.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors used HTTP POST requests to &lt;code&gt;config.cfm&lt;/code&gt;, an expected configuration file in a standard installation of ColdFusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ingress Tool Transfer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1105/&quot; title=&quot;Ingress Tool Transfer&quot;&gt;T1105&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors were able to upload malicious artifacts to the victim web server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITIGATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA recommends organizations implement the mitigations below to improve your organization’s cybersecurity posture based on threat actor activity. These mitigations align with the Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals (CPGs) developed by CISA and the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST). The CPGs provide a minimum set of practices and protections that CISA and NIST recommend all organizations implement. CISA and NIST based the CPGs on existing cybersecurity frameworks and guidance to protect against the most common and impactful threats, tactics, techniques, and procedures. Visit CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cpg&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&lt;/a&gt; for more information on the CPGs, including additional recommended baseline protections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These mitigations apply to all critical infrastructure organizations and network defenders. CISA recommends that software manufacturers incorporate secure-by-design and -default principles and tactics into their software development practices, limiting the impact of threat actor techniques and strengthening the security posture for their customers. For more information on secure by design, see CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/securebydesign&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design&quot;&gt;Secure by Design&lt;/a&gt; webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage Vulnerabilities and Configurations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upgrade all versions affected by this vulnerability.&lt;/strong&gt; Keep all software up to date and prioritize patching according to CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&quot;&gt;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&lt;/a&gt; [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;1.E&lt;/a&gt;].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize remediation of vulnerabilities on internet-facing systems,&lt;/strong&gt; for example, by conducting continuous automated and/or routine vulnerability scans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize secure-by-default configurations&lt;/strong&gt; such as eliminating default passwords, implementing single sign-on (SSO) technology via modern open standards. This also includes disabling default credentials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Segment Networks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employ proper network segmentation, such as a demilitarized zone (DMZ) &lt;/strong&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;2.F&lt;/a&gt;]. The end goal of a DMZ network is to allow an organization to access untrusted networks, such as the internet, while ensuring its private network or local area network (LAN) remains secure. Organizations typically store external-facing services and resources—as well as servers used for DNS, file transfer protocol (FTP), mail, proxy, voice over internet protocol (VoIP)—and web servers in the DMZ.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use a firewall or web-application firewall (WAF) and enable logging &lt;/strong&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;2.G, 2.T&lt;/a&gt;] to prevent/detect potential exploitation attempts. Review ingress and egress firewall rules and block all unapproved protocols. Limit risky (but approved) protocols through rules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implement network segmentation to separate network segments based on role and functionality &lt;/strong&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;2.E&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Proper network segmentation significantly reduces the ability for threat actor lateral movement by controlling traffic flows between—and access to—various subnetworks. See CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/layering-network-security-segmentation_infographic_508_0.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Layering Network Security Through Segmentation&quot;&gt;Layering Network Security Through Segmentation&lt;/a&gt; infographic and the National Security Agency’s (NSA’s) &lt;a href=&quot;https://media.defense.gov/2019/Sep/09/2002180325/-1/-1/0/Segment%20Networks%20and%20Deploy%20Application%20Aware%20Defenses%20-%20Copy.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Segment Networks and Deploy Application-Aware Defenses&quot;&gt;Segment Networks and Deploy Application-Aware Defenses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deploy application-aware network defenses to block improperly formed traffic and restrict content,&lt;/strong&gt; according to policy and legal authorizations. Traditional intrusion detection systems (IDS) based on known-bad signatures are quickly decreasing in effectiveness due to encryption and obfuscation techniques. Threat actors hide malicious actions and remove data over common protocols, making the need for sophisticated, application-aware defensive mechanisms critical for modern network defenses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enforce signed software execution policies.&lt;/strong&gt; Use a modern operating system that enforces signed software execution policies for scripts, executables, device drivers, and system firmware. Maintain a list of trusted certificates to prevent and detect the use and injection of illegitimate executables. Execution policies, when used in conjunction with a secure boot capability, can assure system integrity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application control should be used with signed software execution policies to provide greater control&lt;/strong&gt;. Allowing unsigned software enables threat actors to gain a foothold and establish persistence through embedded malicious code. See NSA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://media.defense.gov/2019/Sep/09/2002180334/-1/-1/0/Enforce%20Signed%20Software%20Execution%20Policies%20-%20Copy.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Enforce Signed Software Execution Policies&quot;&gt;Enforce Signed Software Execution Policies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage Accounts, Permissions, and Workstations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Require &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/fact-sheet-implementing-phishing-resistant-mfa-508c.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Implementing Phishing-Resistant MFA&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;phishing-resistant multifactor authentication (MFA)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;2.H&lt;/a&gt;] for all services to the extent possible, particularly for webmail, VPN, and accounts that access critical systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implement the principle of least privilege &lt;/strong&gt;to decrease threat actors’ abilities to access key network resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restrict file and directory permissions&lt;/strong&gt;. Use file system access controls to protect folders such as C:\Windows\System32.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restrict NTLM authentication policy settings, &lt;/strong&gt;including incoming NTLM traffic from client computers, other member servers, or a domain controller.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/security/threat-protection/security-policy-settings/network-security-restrict-ntlm-incoming-ntlm-traffic&quot; title=&quot;Network security: Restrict NTLM: Incoming NTLM traffic&quot;&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VALIDATE SECURITY CONTROLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to applying mitigations, CISA recommends exercising, testing, and validating your organization's security program against the threat behaviors mapped to the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK for Enterprise framework in this advisory. CISA recommends testing your existing security controls inventory to assess how they perform against the ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques described in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Select an ATT&amp;amp;CK technique described in this advisory (see Tables 2-9).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Align your security technologies against the technique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test your technologies against the technique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze your detection and prevention technologies’ performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat the process for all security technologies to obtain a set of comprehensive performance data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tune your security program, including people, processes, and technologies, based on the data generated by this process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;CISA recommends continually testing your security program, at scale, in a production environment to ensure optimal performance against the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques identified in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESOURCES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-26360&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-26360&quot;&gt;NIST: CVE-2023-26360&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&quot;&gt;CISA: KEV Catalog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/news/best-practices-mitre-attckr-mapping&quot; title=&quot;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&quot;&gt;CISA, MITRE: Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cisagov/Decider/&quot; title=&quot;cisagov / decider&quot;&gt;CISA: Decider Tool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;CISA: Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/securebydesign&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design&quot;&gt;CISA: Secure by Design and Default&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/layering-network-security-segmentation_infographic_508_0.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Layering Network Security Through Segmentation&quot;&gt;CISA: Layering Network Security Through Segmentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.defense.gov/2019/Sep/09/2002180325/-1/-1/0/Segment%20Networks%20and%20Deploy%20Application%20Aware%20Defenses%20-%20Copy.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Segment Networks and Deploy Application-Aware Defenses&quot;&gt;NSA: Segment Networks and Deploy Application-Aware Defenses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.defense.gov/2019/Sep/09/2002180334/-1/-1/0/Enforce%20Signed%20Software%20Execution%20Policies%20-%20Copy.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Enforce Signed Software Execution Policies&quot;&gt;NSA: Enforce Signed Software Execution Policies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/fact-sheet-implementing-phishing-resistant-mfa-508c.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Implementing Phishing-Resistant MFA&quot;&gt;CISA: Implementing Phishing-Resistant MFA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REFERENCES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[1] &lt;a href=&quot;https://packetstormsecurity.com/files/172079/Adobe-ColdFusion-Unauthenticated-Remote-Code-Execution.html&quot; title=&quot;Adobe ColdFusion Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution&quot;&gt;Packet Storm Security: Adobe ColdFusion Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[2] &lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v13/software/S0160/&quot; title=&quot;certutil&quot;&gt;MITRE: certutil&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[3] &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/a3acb9f79647f813671c1a21097a51836b0b95397ebc9cd178bc806e1773c864/detection&quot; title=&quot;VirusTotal GUI File&quot;&gt;VirusTotal: File - a3acb9f79647f813671c1a21097a51836b0b95397ebc9cd178bc806e1773c864&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[4] &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stealthy-new-javascript-malware-infects-windows-pcs-with-rats/&quot; title=&quot;Stealthy New JavaScript Malware Infects Windows PCs with RATs&quot;&gt;Bleeping Computer: Stealthy New JavaScript Malware Infects Windows PCs with RATs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[5] &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Tas9er/ByPassGodzilla&quot; title=&quot;Tas9er / ByPassGodzilla&quot;&gt;GitHub: Tas9er/ByPassGodzilla&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[6] &lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v13/software/S0404/&quot; title=&quot;esentutl&quot;&gt;MITRE: esentutl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[7] &lt;a href=&quot;https://social.technet.microsoft.com/wiki/contents/articles/8548.active-directory-sysvol-and-netlogon.aspx&quot; title=&quot;Active Directory: SYSVOL and NETLOGON&quot;&gt;Microsoft: Active Directory - SYSVOL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
[8] &lt;a href=&quot;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/security/threat-protection/security-policy-settings/network-security-restrict-ntlm-incoming-ntlm-traffic&quot; title=&quot;Network security: Restrict NTLM: Incoming NTLM traffic&quot;&gt;Microsoft: Restrict NTLM - Incoming NTLM Traffic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The information in this report is being provided “as is” for informational purposes only. CISA does not endorse any commercial entity, product, company, or service, including any entities, products, or services linked within this document. Any reference to specific commercial entities, products, processes, or services by service mark, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by CISA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VERSION HISTORY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 5, 2023: Initial version.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zebra ZTC Industrial ZT400 and ZTC Desktop GK420d</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-23-339-01</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cisagov/CSAF&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;View CSAF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;zebra-ztc-industrial-zt400-and-ztc-desktop-gk420d&quot;&gt;1. EXECUTIVE SUMMARY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CVSS v3 5.4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATTENTION&lt;/strong&gt;: Exploitable with adjacent access/low attack complexity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vendor&lt;/strong&gt;: Zebra Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equipment&lt;/strong&gt;: ZTC Industrial ZT410, ZTC Desktop GK420d&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability&lt;/strong&gt;: Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-risk-evaluation&quot;&gt;2. RISK EVALUATION&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to send specially crafted packets to change credentials without any prior authentication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-technical-details&quot;&gt;3. TECHNICAL DETAILS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;31-affected-products&quot;&gt;3.1 AFFECTED PRODUCTS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following versions of Zebra ZTC industrial and desktop printers are affected:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;ZTC Industrial ZT410: All versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ZTC Desktop GK420d: All versions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 id=&quot;32-vulnerability-overview&quot;&gt;3.2 Vulnerability Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.2.1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://cwe.mitre.org/data/definitions/288.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel CWE-288&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A vulnerability of authentication bypass has been found in Zebra Technologies ZTC Industrial ZT410 and ZTC Desktop GK420d. This vulnerability allows an attacker that is in the same network as the printer to change the username and password for the web page by sending a specially crafted POST request to the setvarsResults.cgi file. For this vulnerability to be exploitable, the printer's protected mode must be disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.nvd.nist.gov/view/vuln/detail?vulnId=CVE-2023-4957&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-4957&lt;/a&gt; has been assigned to this vulnerability. A CVSS v3 base score of 5.4 has been calculated; the CVSS vector string is (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3.0#CVSS:3.0/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;33-background&quot;&gt;3.3 BACKGROUND&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE SECTORS:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical Manufacturing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COUNTRIES/AREAS DEPLOYED:&lt;/strong&gt; Worldwide&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPANY HEADQUARTERS LOCATION:&lt;/strong&gt; United States&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 id=&quot;34-researcher&quot;&gt;3.4 RESEARCHER&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phosphorus Cybersecurity reported this vulnerability to CISA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-mitigations&quot;&gt;4. MITIGATIONS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zebra printers running Link-OS v6.0 and later have a protected mode that protects the printer from this vulnerability. Activating this mode disables unauthorized changes and locks the current configuration until an administrator authorizes updates. By default, the secure mode is disabled as it is necessary to generate a password first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about the protected mode and to apply it to Zebra printer products that may be affected, see the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zebra.com/content/dam/zebra_new_ia/en-us/software-printer/utilities/en/admin-files/printsecure-administration-guide-en.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Link-OS Printer Administration Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: The ZT410 industrial printer was discontinued on Oct 1st, 2020. The service and support discontinuation dates are in September and December, 2025, depending on region. Further information regarding security settings and best practices, including &quot;Protected Mode,&quot; can be found in the references of the product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOTE: the GK420d desktop printer was discontinued on Jan 31, 2022. The service and support discontinuation date is April 30, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the product resources, see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zebra.com/us/en/support-downloads/printers/desktop/gk420d.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GK420d Desktop Printer Support Manual&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on this vulnerability, see INCIBE-CERT's &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.incibe.es/en/incibe-cert/notices/aviso-sci/authentication-bypass-zebra-ztc&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Security Advisory&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA reminds organizations to perform proper impact analysis and risk assessment prior to deploying defensive measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA also provides a section for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/resources-tools/resources/ics-recommended-practices&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;control systems security recommended practices&lt;/a&gt; on the ICS webpage on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/industrial-control-systems&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;cisa.gov/ics&lt;/a&gt;. Several CISA products detailing cyber defense best practices are available for reading and download, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://us-cert.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/recommended_practices/NCCIC_ICS-CERT_Defense_in_Depth_2016_S508C.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Improving Industrial Control Systems Cybersecurity with Defense-in-Depth Strategies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA encourages organizations to implement recommended cybersecurity strategies for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/Cybersecurity_Best_Practices_for_Industrial_Control_Systems.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;proactive defense of ICS assets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional mitigation guidance and recommended practices are publicly available on the ICS webpage at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/industrial-control-systems&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;cisa.gov/ics&lt;/a&gt; in the technical information paper, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/uscert/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ICS-TIP-12-146-01B--Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizations observing suspected malicious activity should follow established internal procedures and report findings to CISA for tracking and correlation against other incidents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No known public exploitation specifically targeting this vulnerability has been reported to CISA at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-update-history&quot;&gt;5. UPDATE HISTORY&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;December 5, 2023: Initial Publication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Advisory on Threat Actors Exploiting CVE-2023-26360 Vulnerability in Adobe ColdFusion</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/05/cisa-releases-advisory-threat-actors-exploiting-cve-2023-26360-vulnerability-adobe-coldfusion</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, CISA released a Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA), &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-339a&quot; title=&quot;Threat Actors Exploit Adobe ColdFusion CVE-2023-26360 for Initial Access to Government Servers&quot;&gt;Threat Actors Exploit Adobe ColdFusion CVE-2023-26360 for Initial Access to Government Servers&lt;/a&gt;, to disseminate known indicators of compromise (IOCs) and tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The vulnerability in ColdFusion (&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-26360&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-26360&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-26360&lt;/a&gt;) presents as an improper access control issue and exploitation of this CVE can result in arbitrary code execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA encourages network defenders and critical infrastructure organizations to review the CSA to improve their cybersecurity posture and protect against similar exploitation based on threat actor activity. CISA also urges software manufacturers to incorporate secure-by-design and -default principles into their software development practices to limit the impact of threat actor activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more guidance to protect against the most common and impactful threats, visit CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&lt;/a&gt;. For more information on Secure by Design, see CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/securebydesign&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design&quot;&gt;Secure by Design&lt;/a&gt; webpage.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/04/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CISA has added two new vulnerabilities to its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&quot;&gt;Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog&lt;/a&gt;, based on evidence of active exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-42917&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-42917&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-42917&lt;/a&gt; Apple Multiple Products WebKit Memory Corruption Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-42916&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2023-42916&quot;&gt;CVE-2023-42916&lt;/a&gt; Apple Multiple Products WebKit Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise. &lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; To view other newly added vulnerabilities in the catalog, click on the arrow in the &quot;Date Added to Catalog&quot; column—which will sort by descending dates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/binding-operational-directive-22-01&quot; title=&quot;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the&lt;a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/Reducing_the_Significant_Risk_of_Known_Exploited_Vulnerabilities_211103.pdf&quot; title=&quot;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&quot;&gt;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Catalog vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Catalog vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities&quot; title=&quot;specified criteria&quot;&gt;specified criteria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Releases Security Updates for Multiple Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/01/apple-releases-security-updates-multiple-products</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple has released security updates to address vulnerabilities within Safari, macOS Sonoma, iOS, and iPadOS. A cyber threat actor could exploit one of these vulnerabilities to take control of an affected system. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CISA encourages users and administrators to review the following advisories and apply necessary updates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214033&quot; title=&quot;Safari 17.1.2&quot;&gt;Safari 17.1.2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214032&quot; title=&quot;macOS Sonoma 14.1.2&quot;&gt;macOS Sonoma 14.1.2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214031&quot; title=&quot;iOS 17.1.2 and iPad 17.1.2&quot;&gt;iOS 17.1.2 and iPad 17.1.2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRGC-Affiliated Cyber Actors Exploit PLCs in Multiple Sectors, Including U.S. Water and Wastewater Systems Facilities</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-335a</link>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), National Security Agency (NSA), Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), and the Israel National Cyber Directorate (INCD)—hereafter referred to as &quot;the authoring agencies&quot;—are disseminating this joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) to highlight continued malicious cyber activity against operational technology devices by Iranian Government Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC)-affiliated Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) cyber actors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IRGC is an Iranian military organization that the United States designated as a foreign terrorist organization in 2019. IRGC-affiliated cyber actors using the persona “CyberAv3ngers” are actively targeting and compromising Israeli-made Unitronics Vision Series programmable logic controllers (PLCs). These PLCs are commonly used in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/water&quot; title=&quot;Water and Wastewater Cybersecurity&quot;&gt;Water and Wastewater Systems (WWS) Sector&lt;/a&gt; and are additionally used in other industries including, but not limited to, energy, food and beverage manufacturing, and healthcare. The PLCs may be rebranded and appear as different manufacturers and companies. In addition to the recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/11/28/exploitation-unitronics-plcs-used-water-and-wastewater-systems&quot; title=&quot;Exploitation of Unitronics PLCs used in Water and Wastewater Systems&quot;&gt;CISA Alert&lt;/a&gt;, the authoring agencies are releasing this joint CSA to share indicators of compromise (IOCs) and tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) associated with IRGC cyber operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since at least November 22, 2023, these IRGC-affiliated cyber actors have continued to compromise default credentials in Unitronics devices. The IRGC-affiliated cyber actors left a defacement image stating, “You have been hacked, down with Israel. Every equipment ‘made in Israel’ is CyberAv3ngers legal target.” The victims span multiple U.S. states. The authoring agencies urge all organizations, especially critical infrastructure organizations, to apply the recommendations listed in the Mitigations section of this advisory to mitigate risk of compromise from these IRGC-affiliated cyber actors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This advisory provides observed IOCs and TTPs the authoring agencies assess are likely associated with this IRGC-affiliated APT. For more information on Iranian state-sponsored malicious cyber activity, see CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cyber-threats-and-advisories/advanced-persistent-threats/iran&quot; title=&quot;Iran Cyber Threat Overview and Advisories&quot;&gt;Iran Cyber Threat Overview and Advisories&lt;/a&gt; webpage and the FBI’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fbi.gov/investigate/counterintelligence/the-iran-threat&quot; title=&quot;The Iran Threat&quot;&gt;Iran Threat&lt;/a&gt; webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a PDF version of this CSA, see: &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/aa23-335a-irgc-affiliated-cyber-actors-exploit-plcs-in-multiple-sectors_0.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-335A IRGC-Affiliated Cyber Actors Exploit PLCs in Multiple Sectors, Including U.S. Water and Wastewater Systems Facilities&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(PDF,       567.87 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a downloadable copy of IOCs, see:&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/AA23-335A.stix__0.xml&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-335A STIX XML&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(XML,       15.50 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;





&lt;div class=&quot;c-file&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;c-file__download&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;c-file__link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-12/AA23-335A-IRGC-Affiliated-Cyber-Actors-Exploit-PLCs-in-Multiple-Sectors-Including-US-Water-and-Wastewater-Systems-Facilities.stix_.json&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AA23-335A STIX JSON&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;c-file__size&quot;&gt;(JSON,       10.84 KB
  )&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TECHNICAL DETAILS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This advisory uses the &lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/matrices/enterprise/&quot; title=&quot;Enterprise Matrix&quot;&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK&lt;sup&gt;®&lt;/sup&gt; for Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; framework, version 14. See Table 1 for threat actor activity mapped to MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK tactics and techniques. For assistance with mapping malicious cyber activity to the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK framework, see CISA and MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/news/best-practices-mitre-attckr-mapping&quot; title=&quot;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK® Mapping&quot;&gt;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&lt;/a&gt; and CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cisagov/Decider/&quot; title=&quot;cisagov / decider&quot;&gt;Decider Tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CyberAv3ngers (also known as CyberAveng3rs, Cyber Avengers) is an Iranian IRGC cyber persona that has claimed responsibility for numerous attacks against critical infrastructure organizations.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbsnews.com/pittsburgh/news/municipal-water-authority-of-aliquippa-hacked-iranian-backed-cyber-group/&quot; title=&quot;Municipal Water Authority of Aliquippa hacked by Iranian-backed cyber group&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;],[&lt;a href=&quot;https://industrialcyber.co/analysis/digital-battlegrounds-evolving-hybrid-kinetic-warfare/&quot; title=&quot;Digital Battlegrounds: Evolving Hybrid Kinetic Warfare&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;],[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/israels-largest-oil-refinery-website-offline-after-ddos-attack/&quot; title=&quot;Israel's largest oil refinery website offline after DDoS attack&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;],[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.darkreading.com/cyberattacks-data-breaches/israeli-oil-refinery-taken-offline-pro-iranian-attackers&quot; title=&quot;Website of Israeli Oil Refinery Taken Offline by Pro-Iranian Attackers&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;],[&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CyberAveng3rs/status/1718970041616543922&quot; title=&quot;CyberAv3ngers&quot;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;] The group claimed responsibility for cyberattacks in Israel beginning in 2020. CyberAv3ngers falsely claimed they compromised several critical infrastructure organizations in Israel.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://industrialcyber.co/analysis/digital-battlegrounds-evolving-hybrid-kinetic-warfare/&quot; title=&quot;Digital Battlegrounds: Evolving Hybrid Kinetic Warfare&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;] CyberAv3ngers also reportedly has connections to another IRGC-linked group known as Soldiers of Solomon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most recently, CyberAv3ngers began targeting U.S.-based WWS facilities that operate Unitronics PLCs.[&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbsnews.com/pittsburgh/news/municipal-water-authority-of-aliquippa-hacked-iranian-backed-cyber-group/&quot; title=&quot;Municipal Water Authority of Aliquippa hacked by Iranian-backed cyber group&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;] The threat actors compromised Unitronics Vision Series PLCs with human machine interfaces (HMI). These compromised devices were publicly exposed to the internet with default passwords and by default are on TCP port 20256.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These PLC and related controllers are often exposed to outside internet connectivity due to the remote nature of their control and monitoring functionalities. The compromise is centered around defacing the controller’s user interface and may render the PLC inoperative. With this type of access, deeper device and network level accesses are available and could render additional, more profound cyber physical effects on processes and equipment. It is not known if additional cyber activities deeper into these PLCs or related control networks and components were intended or achieved. Organizations should consider and evaluate their systems for these possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat Actor Activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authoring agencies have observed the IRGC-affiliated activity since at least October 2023, when the actors claimed credit for the cyberattacks against Israeli PLCs on their Telegram channel. Since November 2023, the authoring agencies have observed the IRGC-affiliated actors target multiple U.S.-based WWS facilities that operate Unitronics Vision Series PLCs. Cyber threat actors likely compromised these PLCs since the PLCs were internet-facing and used Unitronics’ default password. Observed activity includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Between September 13 and October 30, 2023, the CyberAv3ngers Telegram channel displayed both legitimate and false claims of multiple cyberattacks against Israel. CyberAv3ngers targeted Israeli PLCs in the water, energy, shipping, and distribution sectors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On October 18, 2023, the CyberAv3ngers-linked Soldiers of Solomon claimed responsibility for compromising over 50 servers, security cameras, and smart city management systems in Israel; however, majority of these claims were proven false. The group claimed to use a ransomware named “Crucio” against servers where the webcams camera software operated on port 7001.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginning on November 22, 2023, IRGC cyber actors accessed multiple U.S.-based WWS facilities that operate Unitronics Vision Series PLCs with an HMI likely by compromising internet-accessible devices with default passwords. The targeted PLCs displayed the defacement message, “You have been hacked, down with Israel. Every equipment ‘made in Israel’ is Cyberav3ngers legal target.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INDICATORS OF COMPROMISE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See Table 1 for observed IOCs related to CyberAv3nger operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&quot;MsoTableGrid tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 1: CyberAv3nger IOCs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Indicator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fidelity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BA284A4B508A7ABD8070A427386E93E0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MD5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MD5 hash associated with Crucio Ransomware&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;66AE21571FAEE1E258549078144325DC9DD60303&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHA1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHA1 hash associated with Crucio Ransomware&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;440b5385d3838e3f6bc21220caa83b65cd5f3618daea676f271c3671650ce9a3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHA256&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHA256 hash associated with Crucio Ransomware&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;178.162.227[.]180&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IP address&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;185.162.235[.]206&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IP address&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK TACTICS AND TECHNIQUES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See Table 2 for referenced threat actor tactics and techniques in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table class=&quot;Table tablesaw tablesaw-stack&quot;&gt;&lt;caption&gt;Table 2: Initial Access&lt;/caption&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technique Title&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brute Force Techniques&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attack.mitre.org/versions/v14/techniques/T1110/&quot; title=&quot;Brute Force Techniques&quot;&gt;T1110&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Threat actors obtained login credentials, which they used to successfully log into Unitronics devices and provide root-level access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITIGATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authoring agencies recommend critical infrastructure organizations, including WWS sector facilities, implement the following mitigations to improve your organization’s cybersecurity posture to defend against CyberAv3ngers activity. These mitigations align with the Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals (CPGs) developed by CISA and the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST). The CPGs provide a minimum set of practices and protections that CISA and NIST recommend all organizations implement. CISA and NIST based the CPGs on existing cybersecurity frameworks and guidance to protect against the most common and impactful threats, tactics, techniques, and procedures. Visit CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&lt;/a&gt; for more information on the CPGs, including additional recommended baseline protections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; The below mitigations are based on threat actor activity against Unitronics PLCs but apply to all internet-facing PLCs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defenders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cyber threat actors likely accessed the affected devices—Unitronics Vision Series PLCs with HMI—by exploiting cybersecurity weaknesses, including poor password security and exposure to the internet. To safeguard against this threat, the authoring agencies urge organizations to consider the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immediate steps to prevent attack:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Change all default passwords on PLCs and HMIs and use a strong password. Ensure the Unitronics PLC default password is not in use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disconnect the PLC from the public-facing internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow-on steps to strengthen your security posture:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement multifactor authentication for access to the operational technology (OT) network whenever applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you require remote access, implement a firewall and/or virtual private network (VPN) in front of the PLC to control network access. A VPN or gateway device can enable multifactor authentication for remote access even if the PLC does not support multifactor authentication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create strong backups of the logic and configurations of PLCs to enable fast recovery. Familiarize yourself with factory resets and backup deployment as preparation in the event of ransomware activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your Unitronics and other PLC devices updated with the latest versions by the manufacturer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confirm third-party vendors are applying the above recommended countermeasures to mitigate exposure of these devices and all installed equipment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, the authoring agencies recommend network defenders apply the following mitigations to limit potential adversarial use of common system and network discovery techniques, and to reduce the impact and risk of compromise by cyber threat actors:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduce risk exposure. &lt;/strong&gt;CISA offers a range of services at no cost, including scanning and testing to help organizations reduce exposure to threats via mitigating attack vectors. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cyber-threats-and-advisories/cyber-hygiene-services&quot; title=&quot;Cyber Resource Hub&quot;&gt;CISA Cyber Hygiene&lt;/a&gt; services can help provide additional review of organizations’ internet-accessible assets. Email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:vulnerability@cisa.dhs.gov&quot; title=&quot;Vulnerability | CISA&quot;&gt;vulnerability@cisa.dhs.gov&lt;/a&gt; with the subject line, “Requesting Cyber Hygiene Services” to get started.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Device Manufacturers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although critical infrastructure organizations using Unitronics (including rebranded Unitronics) PLC devices can take steps to mitigate the risks, it is ultimately the responsibility of the device manufacturer to build products that are secure by design and default. The authoring agencies urge device manufacturers to take ownership of the security outcomes of their customers by following the principles in the joint guide &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/resources-tools/resources/secure-by-design&quot; title=&quot;Shifting the Balance of Cybersecurity Risk: Principles and Approaches for Secure by Design Software&quot;&gt;Shifting the Balance of Cybersecurity Risk: Principles and Approaches for Secure by Design Software&lt;/a&gt;, primarily:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not ship products with default passwords. Instead, either ship products with random initial passwords or require users to change the password upon first use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-11/SbD%20Alert%20-%20How%20Software%20Manufacturers%20Can%20Shield%20Web%20Management%20Interfaces%20From%20Malicious%20Cyber%20Activity_508c%20%281%29_0.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design Alert - How Software Manufacturers Can Shield Web Management Interfaces from Malicious Cyber Activity&quot;&gt;Do not expose administrative interfaces to the internet by default&lt;/a&gt;, and take steps to introduce friction should a device be placed in an insecure state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not charge extra for basic security features needed to operate the product securely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support multifactor authentication, including via phishing-resistant methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;By using secure by design tactics, software manufacturers can make their product lines secure “out of the box” without requiring customers to spend additional resources making configuration changes, purchasing tiered security software and logs, monitoring, and making routine updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on common misconfigurations and guidance on reducing their prevalence, see joint advisory &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-278a&quot; title=&quot;NSA and CISA Red and Blue Teams Share Top Ten Cybersecurity Misconfigurations&quot;&gt;NSA and CISA Red and Blue Teams Share Top Ten Cybersecurity Misconfigurations&lt;/a&gt;. For more information on secure by design, see CISA’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/securebydesign&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design&quot;&gt;Secure by Design and Default&lt;/a&gt; webpage and joint guide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VALIDATE SECURITY CONTROLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to applying mitigations, the authoring agencies recommend exercising, testing, and validating your organization's security program against the threat behaviors mapped to the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK for Enterprise framework in this advisory. The authoring agencies recommend testing your existing security controls inventory to assess how they perform against the ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques described in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Select an ATT&amp;amp;CK technique described in this advisory (see Table 2).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Align your security technologies against the technique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test your technologies against the technique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze your detection and prevention technologies’ performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat the process for all security technologies to obtain a set of comprehensive performance data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tune your security program, including people, processes, and technologies, based on the data generated by this process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authoring agencies recommend continually testing your security program, at scale, in a production environment to ensure optimal performance against the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques identified in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESOURCES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epa.gov/waterresilience/epa-cybersecurity-water-sector&quot; title=&quot;EPA Cybersecurity for the Water Sector&quot;&gt;EPA: Cybersecurity for the Water Sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/water&quot; title=&quot;Water and Wastewater Cybersecurity&quot;&gt;CISA: Water and Wastewater Systems Sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/11/28/exploitation-unitronics-plcs-used-water-and-wastewater-systems&quot; title=&quot;Exploitation of Unitronics PLCs used in Water and Wastewater Systems&quot;&gt;CISA Alert: Exploitation of Unitronics PLCs used in Water and Wastewater Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cyber-threats-and-advisories/advanced-persistent-threats/iran&quot; title=&quot;Iran Cyber Threat Overview and Advisories&quot;&gt;CISA: Iran Cyber Threat Overview and Advisories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fbi.gov/investigate/counterintelligence/the-iran-threat&quot; title=&quot;The Iran Threat&quot;&gt;FBI: The Iran Threat - Web Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/news/best-practices-mitre-attckr-mapping&quot; title=&quot;Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&quot;&gt;CISA, MITRE: Best Practices for MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Mapping&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cisagov/Decider/&quot; title=&quot;cisagov / decider&quot;&gt;CISA: Decider Tool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cross-sector-cybersecurity-performance-goals&quot; title=&quot;Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&quot;&gt;CISA: Cross-Sector Cybersecurity Performance Goals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/cyber-resource-hub&quot; title=&quot;Cyber Resource Hub&quot;&gt;CISA: Cyber Hygiene Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/resources-tools/resources/secure-by-design&quot; title=&quot;Shifting the Balance of Cybersecurity Risk - Principles and Approaches for Secure by Design Software&quot;&gt;CISA: Shifting the Balance of Cybersecurity Risk - Principles and Approaches for Secure by Design Software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/2023-11/SbD%20Alert%20-%20How%20Software%20Manufacturers%20Can%20Shield%20Web%20Management%20Interfaces%20From%20Malicious%20Cyber%20Activity_508c%20%281%29_0.pdf&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design Alert - How Software Manufacturers Can Shield Web Management Interfaces from Malicious Cyber Activity&quot;&gt;CISA: Secure by Design Alert - How Software Manufacturers Can Shield Web Management Interfaces from Malicious Cyber Activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-278a&quot; title=&quot;NSA and CISA Red and Blue Teams Share Top Ten Cybersecurity Misconfigurations&quot;&gt;CISA, NSA: NSA and CISA Red and Blue Teams Share Top Ten Cybersecurity Misconfigurations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/securebydesign&quot; title=&quot;Secure by Design&quot;&gt;CISA: Secure by Design and Default&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REPORTING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All organizations should report suspicious or criminal activity related to information in this CSA to CISA via CISA’s 24/7 Operations Center (&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:report@cisa.gov&quot;&gt;report@cisa.gov&lt;/a&gt; or 888-282-0870). The FBI encourages recipients of this document to report information concerning suspicious or criminal activity to their &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fbi.gov/contact-us/field-offices&quot; title=&quot;Field Office&quot;&gt;local FBI field office&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ic3.gov/&quot; title=&quot;Internet Crime Complaint Center (IC3)&quot;&gt;IC3.gov&lt;/a&gt;. For NSA client requirements or general cybersecurity inquiries, contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Cybersecurity_Requests@nsa.gov&quot; title=&quot;Cybersecurity Requests | NSA&quot;&gt;Cybersecurity_Requests@nsa.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the WaterISAC encourages members to share information by emailing &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:analyst@waterisac.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Analyst | WaterISAC&quot;&gt;analyst@waterisac.org&lt;/a&gt;, calling 866-H2O-ISAC, or using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.waterisac.org/report-incident&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;CONFIDENTIAL INCIDENT REPORTING FORM&quot;&gt;online incident reporting form&lt;/a&gt;. State, local, tribal, and territorial governments should report incidents to the MS-ISAC (&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:SOC@cisecurity.org&quot; title=&quot;SOC | CIS Security&quot;&gt;SOC@cisecurity.org&lt;/a&gt; or 866-787-4722).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REFERENCES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbsnews.com/pittsburgh/news/municipal-water-authority-of-aliquippa-hacked-iranian-backed-cyber-group/&quot; title=&quot;Municipal Water Authority of Aliquippa hacked by Iranian-backed cyber group&quot;&gt;CBS News: Municipal Water Authority of Aliquippa hacked by Iranian-backed cyber group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://industrialcyber.co/analysis/digital-battlegrounds-evolving-hybrid-kinetic-warfare/&quot; title=&quot;Digital Battlegrounds: Evolving Hybrid Kinetic Warfare&quot;&gt;Industrial Cyber: Digital Battlegrounds - Evolving Hybrid Kinetic Warfare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/israels-largest-oil-refinery-website-offline-after-ddos-attack/&quot; title=&quot;Israel's largest oil refinery website offline after DDoS attack&quot;&gt;Bleeping Computer: Israel's Largest Oil Refinery Website Offline After DDoS Attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.darkreading.com/cyberattacks-data-breaches/israeli-oil-refinery-taken-offline-pro-iranian-attackers&quot; title=&quot;Website of Israeli Oil Refinery Taken Offline by Pro-Iranian Attackers&quot;&gt;Dark Reading: Website of Israeli Oil Refinery Taken Offline by Pro-Iranian Attackers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/CyberAveng3rs/status/1718970041616543922&quot; title=&quot;CyberAveng3rs&quot;&gt;X: @CyberAveng3rs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The information in this report is being provided “as is” for informational purposes only. The authoring agencies do not endorse any commercial entity, product, company, or service, including any entities, products, or services linked within this document. Any reference to specific commercial entities, products, processes, or services by service mark, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the authoring agencies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VERSION HISTORY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 1, 2023: Initial version.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Removes One Known Exploited Vulnerability From Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/01/cisa-removes-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CISA is continually collaborating with partners across government and the private sector. As a result of this collaboration, CISA has concluded that there is insufficient evidence to keep the following CVE in the catalog and has removed it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2022-28958&quot; title=&quot;CVE-2022-28958&quot;&gt;CVE-2022-28958&lt;/a&gt; DIR-816L Remote Code Execution Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/binding-operational-directive-22-01&quot; title=&quot;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01: Reducing the Significant Risk of Known Exploited Vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; established the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog as a living list of known Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) that carry significant risk to the federal enterprise. BOD 22-01 requires Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to remediate identified vulnerabilities by the due date to protect FCEB networks against active threats. See the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/Reducing_the_Significant_Risk_of_Known_Exploited_Vulnerabilities_211103.pdf&quot; title=&quot;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&quot;&gt;BOD 22-01 Fact Sheet&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although BOD 22-01 only applies to FCEB agencies, CISA strongly urges all organizations to reduce their exposure to cyberattacks by prioritizing timely remediation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog&quot; title=&quot;Catalog vulnerabilities&quot;&gt;Catalog vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; as part of their vulnerability management practice. CISA will continue to add vulnerabilities to the catalog that meet the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities&quot; title=&quot;specified criteria&quot;&gt;specified criteria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and Partners Release Joint Advisory on IRGC-Affiliated Cyber Actors Exploiting PLCs</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2023/12/01/cisa-and-partners-release-joint-advisory-irgc-affiliated-cyber-actors-exploiting-plcs</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, CISA, the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), National Security Agency (NSA), Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), and the Israel National Cyber Directorate (INCD) released a joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-335a&quot;&gt;IRGC-Affiliated Cyber Actors Exploit PLCs in Multiple Sectors&lt;/a&gt; in response to the active exploitation of Unitronics programmable logic controllers (PLCs) in multiple sectors, including U.S. Water and Wastewater Systems (WWS) facilities, by Iranian Government Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC)-affiliated advanced persistent threat (APT) cyber actors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IRGC-affiliated cyber actors using the persona “CyberAv3ngers” are actively targeting and compromising Israeli-made Unitronics Vision Series PLCs that are publicly exposed to the internet, through the use of default passwords. The PLCs may be rebranded and appear as different manufacturers and company names. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All organizations, including U.S. Water and Wastewater Systems Facilities, are encouraged to review this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa23-335a&quot;&gt;joint CSA&lt;/a&gt; and implement the recommended actions and mitigations. The mitigations are based on threat actor activity against Unitronics PLCs but apply to all internet-facing PLCs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
